<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ecell Items List</string>
    <string name="article1">WANT TO BE AN ENTREPRENEUR? Read on to know how you can be one !</string>
    <string name="article2">Entrepreneurship is all about taking risks and this story is a perfect example to prove it.</string>
    <string name="article3">Read to know how to bootstrap a business.</string>
    <string name="article4">What’s a Bitcoin ? Read on to know why it’s important to be aware with it.</string>
    <string name="article5">Simplest ways to get your priorities sorted and to avoid the common mistakes done by most of the entrepreneurs</string>
    <string name="article6">Worried about clearance for your startup? Well no need to worry anymore since all the hassle has been removed by a new online clearance system. Read on to know more.</string>
    <string name="article7">We don’t need to tell you who’s  Elon Musk but we really need to tell you what you should learn from them</string>
    <string name="article8">Tips to follow in college life to get the job post your graduation</string>
    <string name="article9">What is Kickstarter and how did it start ?</string>
    <string name="article10"> Are entrepreneurs less educated? Read on to find out yourself</string>
    <string name="article1_data">WANT TO BE AN ENTREPRENEUR, THE FOLLOWING POINTS COULD BE REALLY HELPFUL:-
1. Entrepreneurship is a state of mind, a can- do attitude, a capacity to focus on a vision and work towards it. Fear is a mindset, and so is the will to succeed. Your will and efforts will determine your future. You get what you deserve. So if you want something others don’t have , then do what others don’t do.
2. If you push through that feeling of being scared, that feeling of taking risk, really amazing things can happen. Risk is a part of your journey which actually is the most difficult exam. If you don’t take risks, you will end up working for someone who does.
3. Never make excuses and never even think about quitting. Coca cola sold just 25 bottles in their first year. So whatever you are going through, it will be ok.
4. Small efforts every day, end up giving big results. Just keep putting in your efforts, be patient, believe and wait for the result. If you believe, you succeed. If you don’t you can’t.
5. Focus on the team. Building a team of great people who believe in your vision is essential to building a great company. Great things in business are never done by one person. They are done by a team of people.
6. Interns play a really important role. Full of enthusiasm and a will of learning something new, interns are always standing by your side ready to do whatever it takes. Piyush Bansal, founder of lenskart , says he believes in the power of interns so much that he gave major projects to them, to be launched on lenskart.
7. Admit your mistake. Regardless of your position at your position at your company, it is crucial to take ownership of your work and your missteps. Don’t make excuses for things when something has gone off the rails.</string>
    <string name="article2_data">To win big, you sometimes have to take big risks.
In 1970’s Bill gates and Steve Jobs met for a new innovation. Steve Jobs decided to go ahead towards Macintosh; he approached Microsoft and wanted them to build graphical software. The mutually agreed deal was Microsoft would not build any graphical interface for anyone else other than Apple Inc. until a year after Macintosh released and shipped.
Bill gates imagined that graphical interfaces will be going to boom the market if launched. With the courage of pursuing what was just a dream he launched a new and better Operating System with features of graphical Interface like mouse for point and click navigation. This operating system today called as WINDOWS.
Even after being called unimaginative, sued for stealing the idea and challenged to pay 90 cents for every dollar earned from Windows, Gates invested 150 million dollars in Apple when it was ripping off. Gate turned out to be the biggest Philanthropist, Entrepreneur and one of the world’s wealthiest Billionaires the world has ever seen. Call him a thief or an innovator he has been an inspiration to many.
Our success has been based on partnerships from the very beginning. All it takes is talent, determination to achieve what you dream and hard work to make it a reality.</string>
    <string name="article3_data">Accelerating a business from zero is a challenge faced by every budding entrepreneur. More so is the dilemma of choosing self-funding as an option or seeking investors for your business.
So, what separates proverbial winners from the rest? 
They "bootstrap".
But what is bootstrap? How it going to help young entrepreneurs?
*Bootstrap is a technique of starting and using existing resources to create something more complex and effective*
How it relates to business? 
Concerned to business it is \'starting up\' without external help or capital.
How you can bootstrap your business? 
Strategies that truly make the difference and propel you forward are:
1.Take your daily actions and don\'t be afraid of committing mistakes.\n 
2. Be passionate about what you are doing. \n
3. Don’t borrow money if you can.\n
4. Be ready to perform many roles.\n
5. Creative branding.\n
6. Virtual office spaces.\n 
7. Secure all your devices.</string>
    <string name="article4_data">BITCOIN AND EMERGENCE OF A NEW MARKET
Bitcoin is a cryptocurrency and worldwide payment system. It is the first decentralized digital currency, as the system works without a central bank or single administrator. The network is peer-to-peer and transactions take place between nodes users directly through the use of cryptography, without an intermediary. These transactions are verified by network and recorded in a public distributed ledger called a blockchain. Bitcoin was invented by an unknown person or group of people under the name Satoshi Nakamoto and released as open-source software in 2009. 
Cryptocurrencies have led to the emergence of new markets. Currencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum have opened gates for a new kind of market which unlike present money market is controlled by no one. Cyberspace will rise up as the managing body that will handle and maintain such disruptive markets. The near zero transaction cost has made these currencies even superior to the traditional money we are accustomed to using. What can be surely stated is that it is just the beginning and the number of possibilities is endless.
BITCOIN AS AN EVOLUTION
• From generic business mentoring towards technologically-founded mentoring\n
• From proprietary technology towards opensource technology\n
• From distinct community towards socio-material communities\n
FEATURES OF BITCOIN\n
• User Anonymity\n
• No Third-party Interruptions\n
• Purchases Are Not Taxed\n
• Very Low Transaction Fees\n
• Mobile Payments\n
Bitcoin is the next emerging change in the world . It’s the beginning of something great, a currency without a government , a currency to reform the financial system.</string>
    <string name="article5_data">How to get your priorities right?
What is the most common thing to all the startups, big or small? It’s an idea and its execution! But what if there are too many ideas and the actual question that comes up is which idea is to be kept attention on? What if there are too many ideas fighting for focus?
You might think why too many ideas isn’t a good thing. Well, coming up with ideas is great. Trying to execute all of them is not! As it is said
“Digging a well in many places never yields water. 
You\'ll only end up with a hole here and a hole there never going deep enough.”
When you start executing an idea, you get consumed mentally, and two of your most precious resources, time and money also get equally consumed. Sooner or later, entrepreneurs learn that the market doesn\'t take very well to less differentiated ideas. When you spread your resources thin, it\'s difficult to make any one idea standout in a cluttered world.
So, how to deal with this problem? The best way is to start with the execution of those ideas which can tackle the problems of your consumers in the best way. Once you know what your core customers want, list their problems in the order of their needs and wants. What if they don\'t like what you\'ve built?
The answer to that is actually simple. Scrap it and do it over. Or, pick another problem to solve. You may be thinking - but I\'ve spent so much money and time on this!
Remember that you\'ll spend a lot more by going down that rabbit hole.</string>
    <string name="article6_data">Indian Startups will soon get hassle free online clearance
‌This is the first time in India that the state government through Kerala State Industrial Development Corporation (KSIDC) plans to introduce a web portal for online clearance for startups.
The single-window system named K-SWIFT, with an online Common Application Form (CAF), is expected to clear the hassles for startups and industries to apply for permits and clearances. In order to make this convenient the system is being integrated with software called Intelligent Building Planning Management Software (IBPMS) and it is planned for launch this month.
An entity usually requires clearance from 14 to 20 departments, including local self-government department and pollution control board. Thus, K -SWIFT weeds out all manipulations and corrupt practices that earlier used to happen to get the clearance quickly.
K-SWIFT awaits certification from the auditing agency of the central government. Once audited, the agency will refer it to National Informatics Centre (NIC) for rectifying software errors, if any, and then it would be launched.</string>
    <string name="article7_data">When something is important enough, you do it even if the odds are not in your favor."
- Elon Musk
Elon Reeve Musk is a South African-born Canadian American business magnate, investor, engineer and inventor. Elon Musk is a badass . He co-founded PayPal, CEO of SpaceX and Tesla, and recently released plans for a fast-and-cheap transportation system called Hyperloop. Today, Tesla Energy has established itself as a revolutionary energy storage venture for sustainable businesses and homes. This could only happen beacuse Musk dared to challenge the widely accepted reality and changed it. His dedication and perseverance to follow his ambition, the risk taking caliber and a thorough belief in his intutuions made him a revolutionizing transportation both on earth and in space. 
Few things that we larnt from Elon Musk that can help one become a successful entrepreneur-\n
1.Write down your business challenges, break them down into basic components, and then try to figure out how those components can be bettered.\n
2.Consider failure an option and take calculative risk. Don’t be scared of failure especially when you start a new business. \n
3.Nothing should stop you from following your dreams. \n
4.There should be something beyond fame and wealth to motivate you to do great things.\n
Some people don\'t like change, but you need to embrace change if the alternative is disaster.\n
</string>
    <string name="article8_data">Things to do in college life to get the job post your graduation:\n
1. Get Out of the Classroom\n
Attending college gives you a platform to explore and exposure. College classes complete your need in terms of knowledge but for the career, it’s just one aspect of getting a job. At the same time, there is no substitute for it because deep learning only happens in College. Every Company wants to hire an asset so they examine the skills you have, how well you communicate, what’s your aptitude and how well you solve real-life problems and much more.
Internships are the best way to learn.\n
2. Build Friendships and Relationships\n
Friends are a part of college life but one important aspect of friendship is building a network. Thanks to social media you can stay in touch with them forever. Sharing meals, group study, events etc help us learn how to nurture a relationship. This helps us learn how to build a network and at the same time develop a mutually beneficial relationship which is very important in working sectors.
3. Spend Time\n
Networking
And, of course, do more traditional networking throughout your college career. Creating LinkedIn profile is a way to start. In fact, all social media is a great way of staying updated and networking. This helps to know the industry you want to work in. All these will actually help you know how to mold your career to a brighter future.</string>
    <string name="article9_data">The kickstarter story!
Kickstarter needs no introduction. Every day, thousands of startups use Kickstarter to get initial funding. It let’s startup share their idea publicly, the more revolutionary the idea is, the more popular it gets &amp; the more fund it raises! Pebble is one of the leading companies in smart-watches. Initially, it rose funding through Kickstarter, it rose astonishingly! Till date no campaign ever managed to get funding past this milestone. Kickstarter changed lives of thousands of startups founders.
Let’s see how Kickstarter actually started.
In 2002, DJ Perry Chan wanted to play at the fest in New Orleans, but he couldn’t as management asked for a lot of money. Perry thought how great it would have been if the audience could raise fund for him to play at the fest! This simple idea formed the foundation of the Kickstarter project.
Perry decided to start a website using which people can raise funds for their ideas. He moved to New York to present his idea. He met thousands of people, attended an innumerable conference, at last by the end of 2008 he found 3 people who showed genuine interest in Perry’s idea. But none of them knew how to code a website; they decided to hire a developer and used their own money to hire him.
On April 28, 2009, Kickstarter launched officially. It’s worth noting that Perry took 7 years to materialize his idea! Initially, it raised few projects which weren’t interesting and hence got very little funding, after 3 weeks a broke struggling singer starter raised money for her album via Kickstarter, she raised enough money to launch an album which otherwise was not possible for her. According to Perry, this was the first time he felt that people were using his site for the way it was created. The singer’s story got covered by media &amp; Kickstarter kind of got famous, within weeks the number of registered projects increased exponentially &amp; since Perry Chan never looked back.
Till date, Kickstarter has raised 3.2 billion dollars for thousands of startups! It\'s amazing to how such simple ideas can totally revolutionize a complicated thing like funding.</string>
    <string name="article10_data">Well this caption and topic might look really different from the articles or blog you browse through each day
Are Entrepreneurs really less educated?
You know about Steve Jobs, Wozniak, Bill Gates, Mark Zuckerberg and our very Indian being OYO Creator Ritesh Agarwal
All of them are tagged as college dropouts or have a poorly performed academica.
Now let\'s talk about the aftermath. There is a prevelant perception being created by society- Dropping out helps create a billion dollar empire. Agreed or wanna counter? We shall figure out soon enough.
So if you score really low in one test or failed to clear any highly competitive screening exam. One guy steps in with a \'Steve Jobs By Walter Isaacson\' or \'Commencement Speech by jobs at Harvard\' to console or motivate you that life has not ended yet. Though he or she has absolutely correct intention to give you a spark and stand up again, he/she is ethically correct. But does it mean that we should be less inclined towards our mistakes and mess that we have created? Of course not. Entrepreneurial spirit has a major constituent of realizing mistakes and rewinding where it went wrong. It involves learning at each step through mistakes. Though our basic studies and Entrepreneurship can\'t be mixed in same bowl, but they are involved in same root of learning and exploring things
Let\'s flip to the other side of the coin.
We also have Entrepreneurs who are highly educated and skilled. Ankush Singla (Also a speaker at our E summit this year) went to IIT Delhi and Standford University. He took his time with all his patience and did more than a successful startup, founding Coding Blocks. 
These breed of entrepreneurs always take an informed decision by their patience, ability and skills.
So a full stop can be made on a debate of dropping out or not if the only goal is to make a self sustainable business idea.
Now coming back to the \'Less Educated point\'
Education in earlier times was considered as developing a skill set that can be easily absorbed in the industry and or can unlock the new venture.
Yes, education didn\'t mean completing practical files and cramming photocopied notes. It was entirely about the \'SKILLS\' 
We must never forget that Steve Jobs dropped out and held a college GPA of 2.65.
Few know he was really good with designs, number, electronics in school and was an excellent performer. 
Bill was coding faster than his teacher after some time.
They all were Highly Skilled and know what to do and what not to be followed.
They never motivated people to dropout from college
They all know it\'s about the self intuition that makes the way through 
So if you\'re investing your time in college or wherever try to do the one thing that would cement your future, that is develop one or multiple SKILL SETS.</string>


</resources>
